(Penny:)Are you talking to me?
(Raj:)Is there another Penny here?
(Raj:)I had such plans. I had dreams.
(Raj:)I was going to be the Indira Gandhi
of particle astrophysics.
(Raj:)But with a penis, of course.
(Leonard:)It's amazing.
(Raj:)Ever since I was a little boy...
(Raj:)...my father wanted me
to be a gynecologist like him.
How can I be a gynecologist?
I can barely look a woman in the eye.
You know what? I'm not going
to let my parents control my future.
(Raj:)It's time for a showdown.
(Raj:)Somebody give me a computer
with a Webcam.
(Penny:)Okay. Sweetie, I think
that's the Grasshopper talking.
(Raj:)It's about to tell my parents...
(Raj:)...that I'm not riding an elephant
down the aisle with Lalita Gupta.
(Penny:)Okay, calm down.
No one can make you get married.
Why don't you meet this girl,
see what happens?
Haven't you been listening?
I cannot talk to women.
(Dr Koothrappali:)- Raj...
- No, no, let's see how long it takes him.